videograbby.com 2017-06-06

# VideoGrabby: Youtube Downloader - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to us at VideoGrabby. This Privacy Policy document outlines what data VideoGrabby receives and how we store, manage, and protect it. 

This policy is subject to change, and was last updated on November 5th, 2015.

**Logs**

VideoGrabby uses log files, which are files that record information including requested webpage resources, IP addresses, browser type, and timestamps. This information is used by VideoGrabby for troubleshooting, service analysis, and site maintenance. This information cannot be directly linked to personally identifiable information. 

Log files, and any data therein, are not shared with any third party. 

**Collected Information**

VideoGrabby receives and stores information that you enter on the website. This includes requested resources, search queries, and DVR settings like the quality of the recording. This information is stored to monitor and analyze service activity. This information cannot be linked to personally identifiable information. 

All information you enter is voluntary. None of this information is shared with any third party.   

**Cookies**

VideoGrabby stores your preferences in cookies. While these cookies improve your experience by remembering your settings, they're optional. The VideoGrabby service works without cookies. 

Cookies may be stored by third parties via third party content embedded in VideoGrabby, like multimedia players and advertisements. VideoGrabby has no control over the cookies stored by third parties. 

**Questions**

For any questions regarding this Privacy Policy document, please contact us.
